http://www.vanessastump.com/privacy-policy

savorysweetrestaurantsgood livingkidsportraitsaboutcontact
PRIVACY POLICYThis privacy policy helps website visitors understand how Vanessa Stump Photography (www.vanessastump.com) uses personally identifiable information.Personally identifiable information is data that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a person, or to identify an individual in context.This privacy policy provides information about how Vanessa Stump Photography collects, uses, and protects personally identifiable information received from this website.This privacy policy information was last modified on September 22, 2017.PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTEDWhen ordering products, services, or when completing forms on this website, you may be asked to provide your name, email address, phone number, and other personal details. This data allows us to contact you so that I can provide you with additional information about your purchase or for various other purposesCOLLECTING INFORMATIONI will sometimes collect personally identifiable information when you call via telephone, send an email, complete a form, subscribe to a newsletter, or when you provide feedback about products or services.HOW INFORMATION IS USEDYour personally identifiable information can be used to:improve this website to better serve you and other clientsprovide customer service in response to requests for additional informationadminister contests, promotions, surveys, and other website featuressend emails regarding orders or other products and servicesfollow up after a phone call, email, or live chatsend promotional information about new services or productsINFORMATION PROTECTIONAll purchases available through this website are managed via third-party providers that use SSL encryption to protect your payment information. This website is also hosted on a server that is frequently updated with the latest security patches. Industry standard firewalls are also in place.HOW COOKIES ARE USEDCookies are files that a website or service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive. When your browser is configured to allow cookies, this website can recognize your browser and remember certain information.For instance, cookies are used to remember your preferences and which pages you have visited on the Vanessa Stump Photography website allowing for an improved visitor experience. Cookies may also be used to help compile aggregate data about website traffic and site interaction so that better website experiences and tools can be offered in the future. Trusted third-party services also use cookies to track information on our behalf.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers accept cookies by default, but you can modify browser settings to decline cookies. However, modifying that setting may prevent you from taking full advantage all features found on this website. As each browser is different, please search your browser documentation for information about how to deactivate cookiesINFORMATION SHARING WITH THIRD PARTIESVanessa Stump Photography does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This exclusion does not extend to website hosting partners and other parties that assist in operating this website or serving users.All third-party operators have agreed to keep collected information confidential. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Vanessa Stump Photography reserves the right to release information to enforce website policies, when required by law, and when needed to protect the rights, property, or safety of others.THIRD PARTY TRACKINGThis website uses several third-party tools that track visitor behavior. Information about those third-party tools is provided below:GOOGLESome of the tracking tools used by this website may include Google Analytics, Google Search Console, Google Adwords, and Google AdSense Advertising.GOOGLE'S ADVERTISING PRINCIPLESVanessa Stump Photography uses Google services to help provide visitors with a positive website experience. This website adheres to all Google AdWords policies. You can also visit Google's Adwords Policy page for more information.GOOGLE ADSENSE ADVERTISINGGoogle is a third-party vendor that uses cookies to serve ads on other websites. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on previous visits to this website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy. Some of the features that may have been implemented on this website include Remarketing with Google AdSense and Demographics and Interests Reporting.GOOGLE ANALYTICSThis website uses Google Analytics cookies and other third-party identifiers to measure and compile data regarding visitor interactions, ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. This information cannot be used to identify individual visitors.FACEBOOK CONVERSION PIXELFacebook provides tools that allow this website to send data to Facebook, including information about actions that visitors take on this website. This information is used to provide Vanessa Stump Photography with insights about advertising. This is done in full accordance with the Facebook Privacy Policy.Facebook may use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from this website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads.Visitors have the option to opt out of this tracking. Information about how to opt out is found in the Opt Out section below. Vanessa Stump Photography will not combine the information gathered through these tools with personally identifiable information.OPT OUTIf you don't wish to participate in Google advertising tracking, you can opt out using the Google Ad Settings page. You can also opt out of other advertising by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance Consumer Choice Page, the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page, or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.You can also maintain an anonymous visitor session which removes most tracking by using Chrome’s Incognito Mode, Safari’s Private Browsing, or Edge’s InPrivate Browsing.LOG DATAThe Vanessa Stump Photography website collects your computer’s IP address, browser type, browser version, the number and names of the pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, and other statistics used to measure traffic and diagnose technical issues with this website.EXTERNAL LINKSThe Vanessa Stump Photography website may link to other websites. Those websites are outside the control or ownership of this studio. You are advised to refer to the privacy policy of those websites for additional information.CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (CALOPPA)CalOPPA requires commercial websites that collect personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy stating the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom that information is being shared. You can visit CalOPPA for more information for more information.To meet CalOPPA requirements, this website a) allows visitors to use this site anonymously, b) a link to this privacy policy is displayed prominently, and c) the link to this page includes the word “Privacy.”Finally, whenever reasonably possible and relevant, you'll be notified of any Privacy Policy changes via email. You may also update your personal information by contacting mewith any updates.DO NOT TRACK SIGNALSThe Vanessa Stump Photography website cannot honor Do Not Track signals since some of the third-party systems used to track visitor traffic don’t include the technology needed to observe those signals. To learn how to enable Do Not Track in your browser, more information is available.CHILDREN ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA)Vanessa Stump Photography doesn’t market to children under the age of 13.FAIR INFORMATION PRACTICESThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States. To meet the requirements of the Fair Information Practices, Vanessa Stump Photography will notify you via email within seven (7) business days should a data breach occur.CAN SPAM ACTThe CAN-SPAM Act sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and proscribes penalties for violations.Vanessa Stump Photography may collect your email address to:send information, respond to inquiries, answer questions, or address other requestsprocess orders and send information or updates related to ordersmarket to a mailing list after an original transactionVanessa Stump Photography will:use accurate subject lines and valid email addressesidentify messages as advertisementsinclude the physical address of Vanessa Stump Photographyprovide unsubscribe links in advertising emailsIf you would like to unsubscribe from future emails, you can contact me and your email will be removed from future advertising correspondence.ADDITIONAL INFORMATIONFor more information, please contact me any time.
Vanessa Stump, Food Photographer
600 Moulton Ave, No. 404, Los Angeles, CA 90031 - (323) 254-0704 - studio@vanessastump.com
Privacy Policy - Terms of Use
